questions = [
    {
        "question":"What does MAR stand for?",
        "correctAnswer":"Memory Address Register",
        "answer0":"Memory Anchor Register",
        "answer1":"Memory Architecture Register",
        "answer2":"Memory Active Register"
    },
    {
        "question":"What does MDR stand for?",
        "correctAnswer":"Memory Data Register",
        "answer0":"Memory Date Register",
        "answer1":"Memory Drone Register",
        "answer2":"Memory Drain Register"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the function of the CPU?",
        "correctAnswer":"Process data and instructions",
        "answer0":"Store data",
        "answer1":"Move data from one place to another",
        "answer2":"Store instructions"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which storage device is best suited for a phone?",
        "correctAnswer":"Solid State",
        "answer0":"Optical",
        "answer1":"Magnetic",
        "answer2":"Other"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which storage device is a DVD?",
        "correctAnswer":"Optical",
        "answer0":"Other",
        "answer1":"Magnetic",
        "answer2":"Solid State"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is secondary storage?",
        "correctAnswer":"Where data that is stored permenantly",
        "answer0":"Where the boot instructions are stored",
        "answer1":"Where data the computer is currently using is stored",
        "answer2":"Where some data the CPU is using frequently is stored"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is primary storage?",
        "correctAnswer":"Where data the computer is currently using is stored",
        "answer0":"Where the boot instructions are stored",
        "answer1":"Where some data the CPU is using frequently is stored",
        "answer2":"Where data that is stored permenantly"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is an example of secondary storage?",
        "correctAnswer":"HDD",
        "answer0":"RAM",
        "answer1":"CPU",
        "answer2":"ROM"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is an example of primary storage?",
        "correctAnswer":"RAM",
        "answer0":"ROM",
        "answer1":"HDD",
        "answer2":"CPU"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is virtual memory?",
        "correctAnswer":"Memory temporarily stored in the hard drive",
        "answer0":"Memory the computer is using",
        "answer1":"Data stored in the hard drive",
        "answer2":"Memory the CPU is using frequently"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is cache memory?",
        "correctAnswer":"Memory the CPU is using frequently",
        "answer0":"Memory temporarily stored in the hard drive",
        "answer1":"Data stored in the hard drive",
        "answer2":"Memory the computer is using"
    },
    {
        "question":"What stores the BIOS?",
        "correctAnswer":"ROM",
        "answer0":"CPU",
        "answer1":"RAM",
        "answer2":"HDD"
    }
]